http://www.voiceovers.com.au/privacy-policy

×
Need a quote or some more information? No problem!
Wait...
1. Terms
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.
2. Disclaimer
The materials on Abes Audio's web site are provided "as is". Abes Audio makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Abes Audio does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
3. Limitations
In no event shall Abes Audio or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Abes Audio's Internet site, even if Abes Audio or a Abes Audio authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
4. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Abes Audio's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Abes Audio does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Abes Audio may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Abes Audio does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
5. Links
Abes Audio has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Abes Audio of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.
6. Remarketing
Google Analytics remarketing codes are used to record instances where users view certain pages or take certain actions on a website. This will later enable us to offer targeted advertising. If you do not want to be a recipient of targeted advertising, you can opt out through the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications
Abes Audio may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to Abes Audio's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Tasmania without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
- Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
- We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
- We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
- We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
- Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
- We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
- We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Voice Over Artists
Australian Voices
New Zealand Voices
American Voices
English Voices
Canadian Voices
Asian Voices
European Voices
2/65 St John Street, Launceston, TAS 725057 Devonport Road, Quoiba, TAS 7310
Postal
PO Box 1017, Launceston, TAS 7250
E: production@abesaudio.com.auP: +61 3 6424 2466ABN: 14 412 355 131ACN: 140 400 791
2/65 St John Street, Launceston, TAS 725057 Devonport Road, Quoiba, TAS 7310
Postal
PO Box 1017, Launceston, TAS 7250
E: production@abesaudio.com.auP: +61 3 6424 2466ABN:14 412 355 131ACN:140 400 791
Legal
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Follow Us
© Copyright Abes Audio Pty Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
